Guide to Aden-Egypte - album of photographs by Sebah, Fiorillo, Zangaki et al AD.MC.027
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Two men by a grave in the the City of the Dead in Cairo (Caire, Tombeaux des Califes, 213)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000065; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Cairo, Egypt; Tombs; Cemeteries; Mosque-Madrassa of Sultan Hassan; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Men; Group Portraits; French Writing; Mosques
- Qasr El Nil bridge and barracks in Cairo, Egypt (No.281, Port-et Caserne de Kasr-el-Nil)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000066; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Bridges; Nile River; Rivers; Palm Trees; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Military/Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Cairo, Egypt
- A promenade in Gezira (Zamalek), Cairo (Le Caire, Promenade de Gézyreh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000067; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Streets/Roads; Carriages/Coaches; Horses; Transportation; Palm Trees; Street Lamps; Zamalek/Gezira, Cairo, Egypt; Men
- The Palace of Gezira in Cairo (No. 38, Le Caire, Palais de Gézyreh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000068; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Palaces; Zamalek/Gezira, Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Architecture; Fountains; Chandeliers
- The Palace of Gezira in Cairo (Palais de Gézyreh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000069; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Zamalek/Gezira, Cairo, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Street Lamps; Palaces; Buildings; Architecture; Landscapes
- The Palace of Gezira in Cairo (Le Caire, Palais de Gézyreh, Le Nil)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000070; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Water; Palaces; Architecture; Buildings; Zamalek/Gezira, Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Street Lamps; Nile River; Rivers
- The Village of Giza, Egypt (237, Village de Ghizeh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000071; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Rivers; Water; Palm Trees; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Giza, Egypt; Men; Buildings; Group Portraits; Rivers; Nile River
- The Village of Giza, Egypt (Le Caire, Village de Ghizeh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000072; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Palm Trees; Architecture; Buildings; Giza, Egypt; Water; Rivers; Nile River
- People on the road to the Great Pyramids in Egypt (269, Route des Pyramides)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000073; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Streets/Roads; Water; Pyramids; Men; Carriages/Coaches; Horses; Transportation; Group Portraits; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Giza, Egypt
- A portrait of people sitting on the Great Pyramid (Pyramid of Khufu) (Caire, L'Ascension de la Grande Pyramide, 236)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000074; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Tombs; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
- The Pyramid of Cheops (Pyramid of Khufu) adjacent to the Sphinx and the Temple of Khafre (Le Caire, Pyramide de Cheóps, Le Sphynx, Le Temple de Chafra)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000075; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  The Great Sphinx of Giza; Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Tombs; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
- A street in Shubra, Cairo (No.78, Avenue de Choubrah, Caire)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000076; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Streets/Roads; Horses; Carriages/Coaches; Transportation; French Writing; Choubra/Shubra, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Regional/National Dress
- The Mohamed Ali Palace in Shubra (No.33, kiosque de Choubra, Galeries)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000077; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Kiosks/Kushk; Palaces; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Furnishings; Choubra/Shubra, Egypt; Tiles
- The Mohamed Ali Palace in Shubra (Le Caire, Kiosque de Choubra)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000078; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Kiosks/Kushk; Palaces; Architecture; Furnishings; Choubra/Shubra, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- The Tree of the Virgin Mary in El Matareya, Cairo (40, L'Arbre de la Vierge a Matarieh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000079; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Religious Sites; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Albumen Prints
- The Obelisk of Heliopolis ( Senusret I) in El Matareya, Cairo (Obelisque d'Heliopolis, Matarieh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000080; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Tents; Horses; Carriages/Coaches; Transportation; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
- Sphinx of Thutmose III (120, Les Sphynx de Thoulmes III)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000081; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Art; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Egypt
- Statue of Sheikh el-Balad (Kaaper/Ka-aper) in the Boulaq Museum (121, La statue de hois)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000082; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Statues/Sculptures; Photographic Prints; Museums; Cairo, Egypt; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- Statues of Osiris, Hathor and Isis in the Boulaq Museum (123, Osiris, Hathore et Isis)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000083; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Museums; Cairo, Egypt; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Tiles
- Ancient Egyptian funerary sculptures in the Museum of Boulaq in Cairo, Egypt (Le Caire, Musée de Boulaq)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000084; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Museums; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Statues/Sculptures; Furnishings
- Lamps in the al-Hakim Mosque, Cairo (Le Caire, Mosqueé El Haken, Lampes)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000085; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Mosques; Cairo, Egypt; Religious Sites; Furnishings; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- A crystal oil lamp from Sultan Hassan Mosque (Le Caire, Lampe en cristal émaillé du Sultan Hassan)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000086; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Mosque-Madrassa of Sultan Hassan; Religious Sites; Mosques; Cairo, Egypt; Arabic Calligraphy; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Furnishings; Art
- Furniture from the hospital (bimaristan) in the Qalawun Complex (Le Caire, Koursi provenant du moristan Kalaoûm)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000087; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Furnishings; Hospitals; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Cairo, Egypt
- Furniture from the hospital (bimaristan) in the Qalawun Complex (Le Caire, Koursi de Mohamed provenant du moristan Kalaoûm)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000088; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Hospitals; Furnishings; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints
- Mashrabiya (latticework) furniture (36, Muebles arabes)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000089; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Egypt; Mirrors; Arabic Writing
- A mashrabiya (latticework) window covering (354, Moucharabieh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000090; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Furnishings; Egypt; Architecture
- A view of mashrabiya (latticework) windows and awnings (308, Perspective des Moucharabieh)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000091; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Architecture; Buildings; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt
- The courtyard of an Arab school (333, Cour et Ecole Arabe)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000092; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Cairo, Egypt; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Doors/Entrances
- A group portrait of men playing board games at a café (16. Café Arabe)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000093; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Men; Group Portraits; Card Games; Boys; Children; Shops; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Furnishings; Regional/National Dress; Shisha/Hookah/Nargiles; Smoking
- A portrait of men and children sitting at a tinsmiths, lamps and other metalware are on display (N.402, Ferblantier Arabe)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000094; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Shops; Arabic Calligraphy; Boys; Children; Men; Group Portraits; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Markets
- A portrait of a Janissary (Jannissaire, 1036)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000095; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Men; Individual Portraits; Weapons; Swords/Knives; Fezes/Tarbouches; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints
- A group portrait of two men holding staffs (Saïs, Avant-Coureur, 1039)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000096; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Facial Hair
- A portrait of a woman described as falaheen, wearing a niqab (Femme Fellah en marche, 1142)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000097; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Women; Niqab; Photographic Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Painted Backdrops; Jewelry; Studio Photography; Egypt; Carpets/Rugs
- A portrait of a woman described as a bedouin (Type de Femme Bédouine, 1151)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000098; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Women; Jewelry; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; French Writing; Painted Backdrops; Egypt
- A portrait of a man riding a donkey (Bourriquier Arabe (Anier), 1099)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000099; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Donkeys; Men; Transportation; Animals; Individual Portraits; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- A group portrait of men and boys riding donkeys (Le Caire, Aniers)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000100; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Donkeys; Transportation; Men; Animals; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Boys; Children
- A portrait of a boy riding a donkey (94 Bouriquier)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000101; Pascal Sebah, Constantinople (Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  French Writing; Boys; Children; Donkeys; Animals; Transportation; Architecture; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Egypt; Doors/Entrances
- A panoramic view of Alexandria, Egypt (Alexandrie, Panorama, 187)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000102; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Buildings; Mosques; Religious Sites
- A panoramic view of Alexandria, Egypt (Panorama d'Alexandrie, 135)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000103; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Buildings; Architecture
- A panoramic view of Alexandria, Egypt (Panorama d'Alexandrie, 135)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000104; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Alexandria, Egypt; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Buildings; Architecture
- The statue of Mohammed Ali Pasha in Alexandria (Alexandrie, Place des Consuls, La Statue de Mehemet-Aly, 103b)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000105; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Monuments/Memorials; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Palm Trees; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Men
- The Place des Consuls (Midan Tahrir), Alexandria (Alexandrie, Place des Consuls avant l'incendie)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000106; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Kiosks/Kushk; Street Lamps; Fountains; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints; Alexandria, Egypt
- The Palace of Justice (courthouse) in Alexandria (Alexandrie, Le nouveau Palais de Justice, 134b)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000107; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Buildings; Alexandria, Egypt; Street Lamps; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- Hotel Abbat in Alexandria, Egypt (Alexandrie, Hótel Abbat, 131)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000108; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Carriages/Coaches; Horses; Animals; Transportation; Hotels; Alexandria, Egypt; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Shops; Street Lamps; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints
- Sherif Pasha Street in Alexandria (Alexandrie, La rue Chérif Pasha, 106b)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000109; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Carriages/Coaches; Horses; Transportation; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Alexandria, Egypt
- Pompey's Pillar in Alexandria, Egypt (Alexandrie, Colonne Pompée, 113)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000110; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Architecture
- The Mahmudiyah Canal in Alexandria (Alexandrie, Le Canal Mahmoudieh, 122)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000111; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Canals; Water; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Alexandria, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- A village on the edge of a canal in Alexandria (Alexandrie, Village Arabe au Canal, 123)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000112; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Palm Trees; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Water; Canals; Transportation; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- Moharram-Bey Street in Alexandria, Egypt (Alexandrie, Les Allées Moharem-Bey, 155)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000113; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Streets/Roads; Shops; Men; Goats; Animals; Buildings; French Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Alexandria, Egypt
- The Palace of Mohamed Sa'id Pasha in Alexandria (Alexandrie, Le Palais de Saïd Pacha au Mex, 177)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000114; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Palaces; Architecture; Buildings; Alexandria, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- The exterior of Ras el Tin Palace in Alexandria, Egypt (Alexandire, Entrée du Palais de Ras-el-Tin, 109)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000115; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Ras El Tin Palace; Palaces; Architecture; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Doors/Entrances
- The court of Ras el Tin palace in Alexandria, Egypt (Alexandrie, La Cour du Palais de Ras-el-Tin, 164)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000116; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Ras El Tin Palace; Palaces; Street Lamps; Carriages/Coaches; Horses; Animals; Transportation; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Alexandria, Egypt
- Ras el Tin Palace from the Mediterranean in Alexandria (Alexandrie, Le Palais de Ras-el-Tin, 110)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000117; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Mediterranean Sea; Water; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Architecture; Ras El Tin Palace; Alexandria, Egypt; Buildings; Palaces; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints
- Alexandria port (Alexandrie, Vue du Port, 105)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000118; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Boats/Ships; Ports; Water; Transportation; Alexandria, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- Alexandria port (Alexandrie, Panorama du Port, 163)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000119; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Ports; Water; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Alexandria, Egypt; French Writing; Albumen Prints
- Alexandria port (Alexandrie, Vue du Port, 102)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000120; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Boats/Ships; Water; Transportation; Ports; Coast; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Alexandria, Egypt
- A view of people next to a windmill near the port in Alexandria, Egypt (Alexandrie, Panorama du Port, 104)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000121; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Buildings; Coast; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Ports; Water; Alexandria, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- People next to a windmill at the port in Alexandria (Alexandrie, Le Port, Pri du Gabari, 104)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000122; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Donkeys; Men; Animals; Group Portraits; Buildings; Coast; Water; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Ports; Alexandria, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing
- A view of the Citadel of Qaitbay (Alexandrie, La Fortresse Pharos Abul-Abbas, 103)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000123; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Forts/Castles; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Buildings
- A lighthouse in Alexandria, Egypt (Alexandrie, Le Phare, 194)., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000124; Luigi, Fiorillo; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Water; Lighthouses; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Albumen Prints
- A statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_n000125; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Monuments/Memorials; Statues/Sculptures; French Writing; Water; Port Said, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints
- A patterned cover page., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_zbk01; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
  Aden, Yemen; Egypt
- A patterned cover page., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_zbk02; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)
- The back cover of the album 'Aden-Egypte'., Circa 1860 -1890; nyuad_pa000005_zbk03; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 027)